Mr. Lu, are you all right?
What am I doing next?
Break it down!
Come on, think.
They probably hid in here after breaking the window,
waited, and snuck out.
Secure the room right now.
I'll report in.
Damn it, what do I do now?
Check the security footage.
Right.
What the hell happened here?
He's gone.
Call on the team.
We need to secure the area.
Uh, can I use your phone?
Mine's dead.
Idiot.
It's your job to keep it charged.
These distractions can't be coincidences.
You never eat.
How do you make it all night?
It's not that bad.
Um, was that our patient who just went out the front door?
No, he ran.
Our patient's injured.
Xiaolin was right.
Stay calm.
The past will be just as it was.
A lot could have happened.
But Lu Guang made a choice.
And now that choice is fate.
Past or future?
Remain untouched.
Love is real.
Omg...
...